bmtcars.com 2012-09-01

# Privacy Policy | Car News and Reviews | bmtcars.com

**Your Privacy**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

**Site Visits:**  
Whenever you request a page through your browser, navigation and click stream data such as:

* Your IP address  
* Browser and version  
* Operating system  
* Date and time  
* Site from which you came

This information is stored in a log file and/or database. Any search terms that you enter into the SuperVN – Cars and Technology Site Search are also logged. This information cannot be used to identify specific individuals, and is only used for:

* Website and system administration  
* Research and development  
* Anonymous user analysis  
* To gather accurate statistics to advertisers in the form of aggregated data

This information is stored on a secure dedicated server.

**Cookies:**

Cookies are a technology which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a Website. A cookie is an element of data that a Website can send to your browser, and which your browser may then store on your system. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. Doing this will allow you to decide on a case-by-case basis whether to accept cookies or not.

Cookies on this site are used by us, and our ad management system, Cookies are used for:

* Ad tracking,  
* Affiliate tracking  
* Customization of content (i.e. not repeating pop-up windows)  
* Storing login information  
* Statistical site-traffic analysis 

**Collection of Personal Information**  
When visiting SuperVN – Cars and Technology, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Links to third party Websites**  
We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own. 

**Changes to this Policy**  
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion. 

If you have any questions regarding the [privacy policy](http://bmtcars.com/privacy-policy "privacy policy") of SuperVN – Cars and Technology then you may [contact us](http://bmtcars.com/contact-us "contact us") at supervn.com@gmail.com 

Last updated Wed, 22 Dec 2010 02:28
